[Music]
foreign
cut right now but right now the top
story is definitely what's happening
with adani the supreme court judgment
that just came out we were talking about
that and we'll get you some more
reactions on that as well but for now a
lot of the adani group companies have
slipped significantly from the day's
highs and it's still holding up it's not
too bad at all but whether you take a
look at adani Enterprises adani ports
these ones have seen a significant slip
from the top of the trading session
other than that for the market like I
was pointing out it's a half a percent
cut what's you know encouraging is that
the mid cap index the small cap index is
holding on pretty well so uh very flat
for both of these but holding up well
over there the Nifty Bank also not too
bad today is just around a two tenths of
a percent card but survey like I was
mentioning the tough story perhaps once
again well I guess uh you could toss a
coin between the U.S 10 year yield and
the industry but I guess right now
the headlines are a sort of pretty loud
and clear from the Supreme Court we'll
show you caught all the action but
perhaps uh the adani group of stocks
reacting to the news that's come in to
put it in a nutshell the Supreme Court
has directed sebi The Market regulator
to go out and conduct a probe it has
given sebi uh two months time and
basically it has said that sebi needs to
investigate whether there has been any
violation of Securities Law specifically
mentioning uh the the possibility of
non-disclosure of any related party
transactions and remember if you go back
to the Hindenburg report this was one of
the major allegations that was raised in
that report uh sebi then comes out with
its findings and submits it to a special
panel that has been appointed and this
is a panel that consists of some of the
most accomplished luminaries of the
financial and corporate world and then
of course the matter will progress right
now there's still some green on a couple
of those adani stocks but otherwise
pavitra for the market uh just want to
mention out here that we are actually at
very critical levels we should lose
sight of that right now this marker is
trading at budget day lows the little
pop and the excited excitement that we
had yesterday that kind of fizzled out
and that's largely because of what was
happening in the U.S bond market pull up
the U.S 10-year yield the biggest
headline overnight was that we hit that
four percent mark on the U.S tenure and
because of that sentiment is extremely
cautious it's kind of sourd and we
haven't seen a follow through this is
the budget day low this is where we are
at
the other important level of course to
keep in mind is going to be the February
low which is about a hundred points
below where we are trading presently 17
000 255 so psychologically these are
some of the levels that the Bulls are
going to track extremely closely and
hope uh that there is no breach uh below
them I guess pavitra the one good thing
that's working for the market today is
the fact that it's not a very wide
sell-off the broader Market the mid cap
index is still holding up so the selling
is more concentrated on the large cap
side of the screen but as I said I think
these levels are extremely critical and
we need to see if they hold oh
absolutely we will and you know speaking
of some of the stocks which are holding
take a look at the real estate index for
example or you know the PSU banks these
are indices which have seen Sharp Cuts
in the previous few weeks but for this
week if you look at it the real estate
index is up over five percent the PSU
Bank index is up almost five percent so
it's looking quite good over there in
fact if maybe we can pull a few of those
stocks up for you take a look at say a
macro Tech developers you have Suntec
these are just some of the stocks which
are holding up everywhere in today's
trading session on the downside there is
some you know pressure that is being
seen perhaps largest in the I.T space
today so some of those names would be up
for you as well but that's what's
happening in terms of the market action
we're going to keep coming back to this
of course but first up let's get a
conversation going on this show now mm
forgings is the first corporate on our
radar Vidya Shankar uh Krishna joins us
now Vice chairman and managing director
of mm forgings to take some questions on
their Q3 performance as well as their um
you know audible going forward Mr Vidya
Shankar thanks a lot for joining us this
is pavitra you know it's been it's been
a very good showing for your company for
nine months I think you're already
clocking in over a thousand crores of
Revenue I think earlier you're guided
for around 1300 uh cross can you tell us
where that stands would you look to
revise your you know guidance
considering that you've already clocked
in such a solid performance
considering the performance of the last
few quarters I think we would be headed
to about 1400 and a little bit above
that for this year
the CV Market has been pretty buoyant
and uh backed by recent performance or
more end because we could be doing a lot
better than this uh and so we'll be
looking at something closing this year
at around 1400 Plus
okay uh got that Mr vidyashankar just uh
stay on for a second we're getting a lot
of important news from the Supreme Court
today and the flashes on your screen are
of course the next piece big piece of
information that we've got uh the
Supreme Court has basically done away
with the present system of the
appointment of the chief election
commissioner the new system uh is going
to be an appointment done by the
committee which includes the Prime
Minister it includes the leader of
opposition and the Chief Justice of
India so this is also a big big
development that's coming in on of
course a petition that was before the
Apex court so the way the CEC will be
appointed uh will be through this
three-member committee the Prime
Minister the leader of opposition and
the Chief Justice of India so very very
important developments coming in from
the court there as well we'll keep
getting you more details and and some
more color on this judgment and some
more uh details that are coming through
uh in fact I think we have some more
commentary that's coming out let me just
take a look at what some of the latest
developments are so so the Supreme Court
survived judge Constitution bench has
unanimously ruled this the uh the
decision that's flashing in front of you
on the screen the Supreme Court is
saying there's a need to insulate
functioning of the election commission
from executive interference these are
very very important statements coming
out from the Apex Court the election
Commissioners needs uh the same
protection as the CEC the chief election
commissioner and can't be removed by the
government
the code goes on to say that founding
fathers of the Constitution left it for
the parliament to frame law for
appointment of cecs political
dispensations betrayed trust reposted in
them uh the the law is yet to be framed
so this is uh some very important
commentary and observations that are
coming in from the Supreme Court as it
has set in motion a new manner in which
or by which the chief election
commissioner is going to be appointed
three-member committee prime minister
leader of opposition and the Chief
Justice of India so pavitra I think the
Supreme Court has really had a very very
busy morning today and you know this is
obviously a landmark move as well oh
absolutely very big move coming through
once again um you know from the Supreme
Court so those are the flashes on your
screen we'll uh you know talk more about
this and keep bringing you up to speed
with everything that we do get coming
out of the Supreme Court uh just to run
you through it again in case you know
you missed out on any of those comments
the five constitution of the Supreme
Court has directed for an independent
panel
um to you know consisting of the PM the
Lop the cji to appoint election
commissioner so this is what we were you
know bringing up to speed with the five
John five judge constitution of the
Supreme Court bench will decide on the
police seeking independent panel for the
appointment of election Commissioners so
all of these flashes are up on your
screen we will keep talking more about
this uh but uh for now let's go back to
our discussion that we were having with
a corporate on this show mm forgings and
um so you know if I can come back you've
taken us through your Revenue you did
say that you're revising the guidance
upwards to maybe 1400 crores this is for
all of fy23 I do want to ask you on the
margins because you know we have been
talking about the metal prices as well
considering that there has been a fall
and you've already seen an improvement
what can we expect in terms of the
margins because in Q3 we already saw an
expansion to 20.6 percent uh what can we
expect going forward
I would say margins will be reasonably
uh in place I see uh metal prices going
back coming back due to price of coal
already steel prices have gone up in the
last few
couple of weeks at least uh and so metal
prices will be right but as far as we
are concerned metal prices are passed
through so customers will get the
benefit when prices drop and they where
the increase when the metal prices go up
so uh it as far as MMF is concerned it
would be uh largely Revenue neutral
there could be some little bit of timing
differences that we have seen over the
last few years and that's uh that kind
of averages itself out
okay so uh Mr Krishna and uh you know
you've detailed out your Revenue targets
as you're looking at the next couple of
quarters give us some more qualitative
uh you know color on this as well in
terms of where you are seeing growth
coming in from uh you know which are
those clients where uh you know things
are really revved up which markets are
doing the best for you performing the
best for you
yep uh so it'll be the color of mm
project has changed in the last few
quarters from being a forging company
which did some Machining today a
significant portion of our Revenue comes
from uh Machining over 55 percent of our
sales is Machine Products now and we see
this ratio uh going very clearly to 65
and 70 maybe more so we've made a kind
of a leap in uh transition from being a
food shop to being a supplier of
components globally and so that's one
clear Trend over the last few quarters
the other thing that we have seen is our
exports we're normally hovering around
60 of overall sales UH 60 65 today the
situation is totally overturned and
domestic sales constitutes uh 65 uh all
our product sales which is a huge change
so both these are significant Trends as
far as I mean for things is concerned
not that export sales uh you know
obviously I can talk on that yes markets
have dropped compared to last year due
to the geopolitical situation in Ukraine
but by and large if you see uh our
domestic sales have gone uh
significantly up and we expect that
Trend to continue in the months and uh
next couple of years to come as our
export initiatives globally start to
bear fruit once again exports will pick
up as well Mr Krishna and how much of
your experts are from Europe because I
do know last time we were talking about
you know Europe being much software so
how much of this is just Europe related
overall revenues if you see uh pavitra
we are at about uh 15 U.S 15 percent uh
Europe and about seven eight percent uh
South America
so
okay just uh significant number but at
the same time numbers that we could you
know uh push up over time so there's a
lot of Avenue for growth
okay just a very quick final word on
cash utilizations as well uh I believe
your debt is going to be close to 550
crores at the end of FY 23 is we're
looking at the start of the new fiscal
uh what's the comfortable dead Equity
level that you will Target and also
maybe a word on capex that you have in
mind for next year
yeah we have targeted the 500 crores
starting from the beginning of this
fiscal so and we are about 200 crores
into it balance 300 is uh to be spent
over the next I would say five to six
quarters so one quarter of this year and
uh four more of next year FY 24 and
maybe a little bit into fy25 so this
should take us uh comfortably uh we're
looking at turnover in the region of
about 2400 odd crores so that's fine and
as far as
debt Equity is concerned we are pretty
comfortable uh net debt Equity right now
is rather lowered about 0.4 so debt
levels are pretty comfortable and as uh
you know we marched into the next year
we could see us taking on a little bit
more of that of course we're also
pairing debt even as we speak uh every
year our repayment is around 90 to 100
crores uh we may possibly stabilize at
these levels of long-term debt all right
you could stabilize at these levels for
long-term debt Mr Christian we leave it
at that today but thank you very much as
always for stopping by and speaking with
us on the outlook for the company that
is the management of mm forgings the
stock is a little bit under pressure
today and you know for the past year as
well it has been pretty range bound uh
just around five percent higher but
that's uh the conversation that we were
having we don't need to get into a short
break now on the other side we will talk
uh you through what's going on with the
weather conditions we're gearing up for
a scorching summer the IMD has been
warning about this I will get us the
latest
thank you
[Music]
foreign
trading hour it is time to talk
Commodities and it's the rising Mercury
that is dominating headlines in the
commodity Universal plate let's go
across to Manisha for the latest Manisha
either it's China or it's this Rising
Mercury so you tell us uh what's the
latest on the temperature well I can say
this much of the heat is definitely on
right now whether it's on asset classes
Commodities or the weather on that side
and we have seen Feb come out as the
hottest since 1901. it was warmest
February in Delhi after 122 years there
and currently as well when you look at
the weather temperatures we are 3 to 11
degrees above normal for various States
and that's exactly the kind of advisory
the IMD and skymet are putting out as
well so March and April we are looking
at higher temperatures here for
Northwest as well it was the hottest in
122 years as we have seen and there are
concerns coming in from labor
construction all of those sector as well
so Feb also has recorded 68 of a
rainfall deficit and anti-cyclon over
Arabian Sea has been one of the reasons
that you have seen the temperatures
continue to to increase the markets also
are looking at 2023 which is expected to
mark an end of La Nina event what does
Larina mean well it means that you have
the above surface temperature on the sea
slightly cooler than normal that is what
gives you Breeze and gets you colder
temperatures and this is an event that
we have seen for last three years pardon
me but that seems to be changing now and
El Nino will mean that you have warmer
temperatures and that will see increase
in temperatures coming in there so their
night temperatures May remain above
normal is the IMD forecast now coming in
for the month of March they also are
anticipating scattered rainfall and that
could temperatures are under control for
some of those days there AMD also go on
to say that you are going to expect
three to nine percent of temperatures on
the higher side and that they will
provide color-coded Heat Wave warnings
from first of March which we have seen
already start to come in there
skymet also has been talking the same
thing and they also have warned that it
is going to be about States like Gujarat
Rajasthan and verba which could be
looking at 40 degrees in sense of
temperatures in the second week of March
itself so March April May and June
before the monsoons really begin it is
going to be a very harsh Summers as to
say the higher temperatures also are
giving a lot of crop concerns right now
which may see an impact in sense of
deterioration in output as well as yield
there the important crops that we're
looking at right now one is wheat the
other is mustard and Chana as well these
are the standing crops and there could
be some impact of the Harvest and these
crops coming into the markets also then
the anticipation also of higher
consumption of electricity for air
conditioning and irrigation is something
that the street is as of now
anticipating and putting much higher
numbers for that as well so uh just to
explain on what heat wave really means
when you look at planes if it is mercury
above 40 degrees or four and a half
degrees above normal it is called a heat
wave when you're talking about Hill
stations or mountains Mercury above 30
degree will tell you that and when you
talk about coastal areas anywhere
temperature which exceeds 37 degrees is
called the Heat Wave and that's exactly
what we are anticipating for the month
of March all right Manisha thanks a lot
for getting us all of the latest on what
the summer season is likely to look like
so in addition to an early onset you're
also likely to get a severe summer this
time around in fact we've been talking
to a lot of consumer companies and we do
have a very special chart with the
management of Crompton consumer also
lined up for you on this show so stay
tuned we you know we spoke to them about
what the demand is looking like in this
situation so we will bring you that but
for now we have to get into a short
break it is a 78 point cut on the Nifty
we'll discuss the market technicals with
Vishal malkan when we come back
[Music]
thank you
welcome back 17 370 that's where we are
at on the Nifty so we're off the days
low but it is still an 80 point card
that we are seeing the mid cap index
however has moved into the green and
like we've been pointing out all through
the morning it is the broader markets
which are holding are much better the
mid cap index the small cap index are
faring a lot better than what we are
seeing on the key uh Frontline index in
fact the Nifty bank is also doing a
little bit better it is right now around
to two tens of a percent cut but holding
up much better uh let's get Vishal in
for a technical check on the market
Vishal you know we did slip below that
crucial budget day low that we've been
talking about as well today we're off
those levels now at 16 370. how do you
see it panning out from here you know
yesterday we did get a bit of a bounce
but um seems like it was restricted to
perhaps a one-day move over there on on
the back of what we call globally as
well how do you look at today's move on
just an index level
yeah hi good morning I think uh Nifty
and bangalty both uh in a way are
holding on to those budget days those in
a way Nifty has slightly broken that but
we can consider that much because those
levels of 17 300 and 400 are very strong
on charts on the weekly as well as the
monthly as well as the retracement
levels so it won't be easy to break
those and especially other stocks like
Blue Chip stocks are also holding on to
those budget day lows so I think it
should hold on to this it may
consolidate for a few days but it should
see a nice bonds from here in the coming
days
okay so we're expecting a bounce in the
market Vishal uh that's interesting so
do you have any ideas on the upside
individual stocks any Longs that you are
working with
yeah so the stocks which are tracking
right now the one of them is IEX which
has broken out of the resistance of 145
and sustaining about that with good
volumes and daily and weekly charts have
got better patterns so I think we'll go
with a Buy on that with a stop of 145
right now for a target of 160 to 165 in
the next few trading sessions and the
second one would be India cement which
has also bounced back nicely in the last
few days and forming bullish pattern on
daily as well as weekly so I'll go with
a Buy on that with a stop of one 94 for
targets of 220.
all right IEX and India cement special
thanks a lot for stopping by for that
quick check on the market we don't need
to get into a short break but there's
lots more coming up for you on the other
side so stay tuned
[Music]
foreign
coming in from Mr Gotham adani on the
developments at the court today I'm just
going to read the Tweet out verbatim uh
Mr adani says the adani group welcomes
the order of the honorable Supreme Court
it will bring finality in a time-bound
manner truth will prevail unquote uh
time bound obviously is the operative
word over here because remember what
we've heard from the Supreme Court today
is that sebi has been given two months
time they have to conduct a probe and
submit their findings to that special
panel that has been nominated which
includes the likes of Mr Nandan nilakani
Mr OPI bhart
and of course some judges Justice supre
himself so it includes six members
including Justice supre and the report
is to be submitted to this panel in two
months time and therefore that talk
about uh finality in a time-bound manner
okay with that let's uh move on to some
other stories as well and this is an
important one especially when it comes
to health insurance we're learning from
sources that health insurance premiums
are likely to have been increased by
approximately 15 to 18 percent Yash is
joining in with all the details yes this
is a pretty steep increase in at least
some of the plans what's causing it and
what are insurers saying well survey
that's correct a steep increase in
health insurance premiums and almost all
uh General insurance companies and
Standalone health insurance companies
have made this increase the reasons are
different for some it's uh the inability
to be able to increase the premiums for
some years which has caused the Steep
increase for some it is high claims
which they've received post covet as
well because of which this increases
come about uh in in totality what we're
going to understand is that the general
insurance industry in the Standalone
health insurance industry together
they've increased premiums by about 15
to 18 percent on the health portfolio of
course not uh the best news for policy
holders but certainly an important and a
positive and a needed move for health
insurance and general insurance
companies that's because health
insurance portfolio itself contributes
about 35 to 40 percent to the total
premiums which are these companies are
essentially raised uh talking about
individual companies ICICI Lombard is
likely to have increased health
insurance premiums by about 10 to 15
star Health they've increased our
premiums for their plan which is Family
Health Optima by 25 Family Health Optima
plan itself contributes about 45 percent
to Star Health's total premium so those
are the important numbers there New
India the PSU company uh some respite
for policyholders there as the company
has not taken any hike as far as the
premiums for the health insurance is
concerned htfc or go another large
company they've increased their premium
by about 25 care Aditya birla Health
Reliance General Health insurance they
likely to have increased their premiums
in the range of 8 to about 20 percent
all right thanks a lot for getting us
all of those details there like ash was
pointing out you know we did speak with
the management of star Health as well
and they're saying that medical
inflation as well as rising claims is
what has led the company to write you
know to raise their premiums by this
quantity like Yash said it's 25 for the
family Optima plan but with that we have
to get into a short break on the show
when we return we're going to bring you
X apps from our conversation with
Crompton CEO Matthew jobsticking
foreign
into trading hour and let's get you a
conversation now on the sidelines of the
nascom technology and Leadership Forum
CNBC TV 18's children caught up with
Crompton CEO Matthew job and asked him
about the company's transition to star
rated ceiling fans for greater Energy
Efficiency the impact of this move on
their business the Crompton CEO in fact
also discussed margin pressures and how
the summer demand is really panning out
considering that we do have an early
onset listening
we still almost two cooler fans a year
and I think almost 80 percent of that is
ceiling fans
and from 1st of January this year I
think we had to completely reject the
portfolio to make sure that they made
the Newbie standards so I think for
almost six to nine months I think our
entire you know r d teams have worked
you know hard to make sure that the
entire content portfolio which is of in
excess of 500 skus actually redesigned
to meet the the new Norms so so yeah I
mean that that work took I think quite
some effort especially in terms of
deployment of the r d resources now
having done that of the products have
all our ceiling fans uh have been
converted to to star rated fans starting
from January this year I think our
current objective is to get these
Superior Products to the consumers hands
as quickly as possible uh and you know
not only to get them to the consumer
hand as quickly as possible but to do so
you know with the minimum price increase
and also then to be able to communicate
to Consumers that energy efficient fans
which were traditionally much more
expensive are now within everybody's
reach so we're building also a TV
Campaign which will bring this idea of
Energy savings within your reach right
to to our to potential consumers across
the country right
have to take a price increase for the
portfolio how much is that and also if
you can run me through what are the
inventory levels with trade then right
now and what about non-star rated and
star rated so so I would say you know
cost increase of one star rated fans
versus non-star rated fans which was
being sold till the last quarter is
about 15.
because the entire you know products
have to be you know upgraded to meet the
new requirements having said that
obviously it was not reasonable to try
and pass 15 increase to the consumer
because you know I think the the fans
industry has already passed in the last
year and a half almost 20 percent uh
price increase to the market because
most companies were facing um cost
inflation indexes of 30 uh so what we
have done is we have passed roughly five
percent increase to the to the consumers
and our objective and goal has been to
continue to work you know our r d people
to try and eliminate or or at least if
not eliminate minimize that the cost
increase that has happened uh that's
that's one I think so going forward you
know our primary objective is one to
make these star rated funds available as
at as lower price Delta as possible
number one second in terms of your
question on um on on inventory of both
non-star rated fans and star rated fans
I think our objective always has been to
get these Superior Products to the hands
of the consumers as quickly as possible
so even in the October November December
quarter uh you know we were very careful
in terms of building up stocks okay or
in pushing extra stocks to the channel
because we believed that you know the
faster we could get these new products
to the hands of the consumers the better
it would be for everybody
fans are concerned I think at this
moment in February or February it was
February and I think these stock levels
in the trade of non-star rated fans is
pretty much zero or close to zero okay
uh for some for some of the other brands
they could be a little higher because of
the fact that a lot of stocks have been
pushed in the last quarter what's your
outlook for the pumps business then
because a lot of slow down flag there as
well you're right bombs has been soft
for a while I think that's been cost by
by two or three factors one I think uh a
lot of competitors who have
traditionally been only playing in
agricultural pumps because of the fact
that agricultural pump business itself
was struggling expanded into residential
and they came in with very low prices
and you know initially we decided not to
respond immediately
that's one so obviously we did start to
lose some volume because with the fact
that we did not want to act on prices
very quickly uh now having said that in
the last quarter maybe towards November
December we decided that we needed to do
some pricing action so that's been done
and we started to see some improvement
already right the second also I think uh
an area which is of importance for us is
again to build some Superior proposition
in pumps if you know a lot of consumer
research and we've identified that you
know the two critical consumer benefits
are one how quickly do you fill the the
tank correct and second is how durable
are the pumps so you know based on these
two parameters if you identified we have
reject the entire portfolio especially
in residential so those products are
started going into Market in December
right we have a you know collected the
prices to make ourselves more
competitive and third I think we are not
advertised problems in the last 15 years
okay so you know coming this season
April June we will also advertise pumps
because as I mentioned some time back I
think it's not only enough to to have a
good idea but then you need to you know
design products around and then
communicate that to the consumers that's
the third part of that of that entire
equation which we will which will
Implement and that I think we'll get
pumps back to double digit growth right
in the short term how much was this
price correction that you talk about and
also in other categories also I think
you did have to you did take some
pricing actions of some correction there
okay so I would say we have collected or
reduced prices by roughly five percent
okay because you know we felt that the
difference with with competition had
become unsustainable correct but that's
only the first part you know just you
cannot only keep dropping prices and
compete that's why we took the second
action in terms of rejecting the
portfolio around relevant consumer
benefits and third can communicate in
some of the other categories you know
it's been more tactical like I mentioned
30 cost increase on fans we are possibly
20 okay second when this star rated fans
got got launched cost increases 15 we
only passed five percent uh and the rest
we are trying to manage through one you
know better management the cost side
you know and second is you know better
management of the mix so I think that's
how because I think it's very important
that we don't start to lose share right
even if it means you know for a short
period of time we have to compromise on
margins a little bit right so that's how
we are trying to look at this whole
business going forward I come back to
the share in a little bit but I wanted
to then understand margins also right
margins or sharp drop in the last
quarter as well but there has been some
softening of uh raw material price of
commodity prices so where's the pressure
coming in from what's the Outlook like I
would say a last quarter I think uh
gross margins that's actually you know
they were intact okay I think the reason
why you saw the company's profitability
wrote a little bit was because our sales
did not grow you know as usual normally
we would be delivering 10 to 15 growth
in our quarter last quarter was negative
okay and that's why you saw the margins
you know at an even level erode but
fundamentally the gross margins are you
know are where you know where they have
been for quite some time okay so I think
the challenge or the the key objective
in in the short term is to get growth
back which is why we have taken some
action tactically on some of the areas
like pumps uh we believe that if you're
able to deliver double digit growth we
will continue to have industry leading
profitability optimizing our Focus going
forward instead of trying to maximize or
keep or manage profits on a quarterly
basis you should try and ensure that the
long-term you know growth of the company
is is kept intact okay and that's how we
are trying to rebalance you know growth
and profit going forward and and the
summer demand I wanted to understand how
do you expect summers are supposed to be
harsh there's an early onset of Summers
and several regions also so what is your
outlook for demand like do you think
that the softness in the past couple of
quarters can be you know uh met or
overcome this time for the air coolers
business for the fans business yeah I
think you know for unfortunately except
you know for the for the last two three
years I think the summer quarter has
been disrupted because of kovid correct
lockdowns and so on and so forth less so
last year but the two years before that
uh we think that you know a lot of this
short-term disruption which we had
because of these phase in phase out of
fans would be done by then and also
given the harshness of the summer and
also February has been the hottest
summer on record right so we think in
the April June quarter will be will be
reasonably strong for uh for especially
for fans pumps and air coolers okay so
we do we are optimistic that things will
start to look up in spite of the fact
that there is still some commodity
headwind
because in the last uh two months I
think Commodities again have have gone
up by roughly 10 percent
okay so that's the word coming in from
Crompton and with that we are completely
out of time on this edition of trading
hour thank you very much for watching do
stay tuned halftime report coming up
next
foreign
[Music]